And with that, it concludes our session on tools.
And at this point, you are probably an expert on tools because you've gone back and you've added in
the extras, like giving your LLM the ability to book flights in that it can print it to your output.
So congratulations on getting here.
Now you are very well versed in transformers.
You can code against the frontier LLM APIs, and you can build AI assistants with user interfaces and
using tools for more expertise.
Tomorrow is completing week two, bringing introducing agents to the mix, a super juicy topic.
We're going to talk about how agents can carry out more complex sequential activities, breaking them
down into smaller steps, and having specialist AIS that can handle each of those steps.
And the specific area we're going to look at is introducing some multi-modality.
We're going to have specialists that can take care of things like creating images, because that's going
to be fun, and it is going to allow us to build an even more sophisticated business application.
So with that, I'll see you for the next one and very much looking forward to it.