So what we're now going to do is we're going to look at some models in practice and start to compare
them and ask some questions.
Some of the questions we're going to ask, we're going to ask how do I decide if a business problem
is suitable for an LM solution?
Because it's again useful for us to hear the answer and to learn from it.
But also it would be good to see.
I imagine you'll see that that's a question that none of the models will have any problems with, and
it'll be great to see that.
I will also ask a question which I think is interesting because it's sort of introspective.
It sees whether the models have a sense of of what they are by saying compared to other LMS, what kinds
of questions are you best at answering and where do you where do you have challenges and which other
LMS have capabilities that complement yours?
So it's an interesting one to see if they even recognize that they are LMS and can sort of assess themselves
against others.
And then a question which surely will be something which which they will struggle with, because it's
something that I would struggle with.
What does it feel like to be jealous?
A yeah, a philosophical and a very human centric question, and then a rather interesting one.
How many times does the letter A appear in this sentence?
And if you do a quick count there, I think you'll find that it appears four times, and we'll see whether
the models can figure out that it appears four times.
And then there are a couple of other interesting things I have up my sleeve to ask.
So we'll be going through and the screenshots you see here ChatGPT, you'll see Claude, Gemini and
Commander Plus from cohere, and we'll try the other ones too.
And again, please do bear in mind, try looking and understanding the differences and seeing how you'll
be able to apply this to your own model selection.
See you in a second.