It's remarkable.
But you are now at the 95% point.
There's 5% remaining of this course.
Uh, maybe it's not remarkable because hopefully you're feeling like you've built up such strong skills
and you're getting really experienced.
You probably saw some of the problems I was having a moment ago, before I did, and knew exactly how
to sort them out.
So what you can now do is this long list of things.
I could no longer fit it into three bullets, and I struggled to fit it into four.
There's far too much stuff.
I had to put structured outputs in here in the first bullet, just to try and fit it in, but there's
so much that you can do across closed source and open source models, calling them in all sorts of ways
now, including productionizing them.
Uh, and now we change topic to talk about agent workflows Agentic frameworks.
This is something that we touched on in previous weeks.
Uh, we, we had, we used uh, function calling, which we said at the time is a kind of light version
of, of agent workflows where you do have, um, a task that's being divided into smaller tasks with
specific models carrying out tasks.
And as you take that up a notch and start to get to an environment like we've been talking about this
week, where you have multiple models that are all working independently, potentially being organized
by a planning task, a planning agent, and then put together in some sort of a framework which has
memory and which can, uh, live beyond outside the context of a human necessarily interacting with
it.
You're getting to a full on agentic workflow, and that is what we will be talking about next time.
And I'm really excited about it.
And I will see you then.