And with that, amazingly, you completed day one of week two already and that gets you to the 15% point
towards your goal of being an LM Engineering Master.
So congratulations on getting to the 15% point.
Let's talk about what you're already able to do.
As you know, you can describe Transformers.
And that includes all of the context window tokens, API costs and the like.
You can talk about the six leading frontier LMS.
You can now confidently use OpenAI's API with streaming, with markdown, with JSON.
And now in addition, you can use the Anthropic and Google APIs, and you've hopefully got even deeper
insights into that structure of messages, that list of dicts that is going to feature from time to
time, as you will see tomorrow.
Tomorrow is a day that I've been looking forward to for a long time.
I am going to be gushing gushing about Gradio, which I think is an absolutely fabulous platform and
you are going to see why yourself.
You're going to see why I love it so much, and I'm hoping that you're going to love it too.
We're going to create a simple UI with Gradio, and we're going to hook it up to Frontier Models, and
it's going to be really, really easy.
And I will see you then.