And so at the beginning of this week, we started by talking about hugging face pipelines.
And you used all the different pipeline.
Not actually not all of them, because there's so many, but we use many of the most common pipelines
to do every day inference tasks.
And now today we looked at Tokenizers and you are well versed in Tokenizers, and hopefully a lot has
come together in terms of your understanding of what they mean and how they work, and special tokens
and all the like.
So next time, next time we start to work with models and this is when we can use the underlying hugging
face code that is a wrapper around PyTorch or TensorFlow code to generate text and compare the results
across multiple open source models.
And that's going to be a ton of fun and I'm looking forward to it.