I am delighted to welcome you to the first day of our eight weeks together as you join me on this adventure
to master AI and LLM engineering.
Now look, it's customary in these things to start with me giving an introduction about myself.
Tell you about the course.
Tell you what you all accomplish over eight weeks.
ET cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
But no, this isn't that kind.
Of course it's not what I'm going to do.
We have plenty of time to get back to that later.
What we're going to do now is get right into the thick of it and get you set up and using an LLM on
your computer right away for a useful purpose.
So without further ado, go on to the next video and I'll get you set up.