Well, another congratulations moment.
You have 40% on the way to being an LM engineer at a high level of proficiency at this point, in addition
to the stuff that you you know very well about frontier models and open source models, you can also
now use the Hugging Face open LM leaderboard to compare different models against a number of hard metrics,
and you've got a great understanding of the difference between these metrics, what they score and why,
and the limitations of the metrics as well.
Hopefully you spent some quality time yourself now with the LM leaderboard, getting familiar with the
different models.
Next week there is some more on leaderboards to do.
I hope you're not bored of leaderboards yet, because we're going to look at a bunch of others that
are used to compare more specialized things about models, and we're also going to look at ones that
bring together open source and closed source, which will be very interesting.
We are going to talk about real world use cases of LM solving commercial problems.
I imagine everyone has experienced this in your workplace and in just using products all the time.
But I want to go through a few examples and have you think about other places where Llms have been applied
to solve hard commercial problems beyond the obvious, and that should equip you to be able to confidently
choose the right LM for your task at hand, so that you know when you're facing a commercial project,
how do you go about navigating the huge number of possible models and select the right couple to build
a prototype for?
So with that, I will see you next time.
We've got lots to do.