Well, we took on a lot today and we seem to have been successful.
These red icons that you see on this agent workflows diagram have been built, and we have them in the
agents directory in the week eight folder.
And so do spend some time looking through them and getting some appreciation for what we've built.
And with that it brings us to a summary end of end of the day slide, which is inching ever closer to
the summit of the mountain.
You are at the moment at 92.5% of the way there.
And I hope you're starting to really get that sense that you are becoming advanced.
You're taking the conversion from being confident with this stuff to being an expert at this point.
You can also, along with everything else you can do, you can now deploy models to production, including
through modal, to call them remotely on the cloud and also building some pretty heavyweight rag pipelines
that look over a big Croma database to build context to send to OpenAI.
And combining that with machine learning models as well, to build a robust production solution.
Next time we're going to look at some more things, we're going to look at something called structured
outputs, which is a way that we can connect with OpenAI and enforce that.
The response comes in a particular specification.
It's something that's relatively new, and it's good for us to to add that to your skill sets to your
tool belt.
And it's just going to be about solving some more problems using models as you build and build expertise
and keep upskilling.
So I'm so excited and so pleased with our progress.
I'll see you next time when we look at structured outputs.