And already that wraps up day two.
Now that you have built that solution.
And congratulations on that.
And I would love to see it.
By the way, if you want to share it, uh, you've got some experience with summarization both with
OpenAI and with llama.
Next time we're going to have some fun with Frontier models, we're going to look at six of them.
You're going to get sleeves rolled up, hands on experience with them so that we get a good sense,
a good intuition to the differences between them.
We're going to use some of the latest and greatest versions, and we're also going to see some areas
where they struggle.
So looking forward to that.
I will see you then.