And once again, it's that moment when you take a pause and congratulate yourself on another day of
skills learned and fantastic achievements of being able to be an expert in the hugging face Transformers
library.
In addition to using pipelines and tokenizers, you can now use models.
You can look at models, you can load different models, and you can run models to do hopefully more
than just tell jokes, but also other kinds of text generation tasks like the ones we've done in previous
weeks.
Uh, you, uh, also can, of course, code confidently with frontier model APIs and build AI assistants,
including multimodal AI assistants, and use tools.
So all of this together, uh, totals a significant amount of learning that you've done already, with
a lot more exciting stuff ahead.
The next session, we're going to do one more project with Tokenizers and models, just to give you
a little bit more experience.
Uh, and we're also going to yeah, just keep keep running inference on open source models and implement
an LLM solution that's going to combine a frontier model call with an open source model call.
And it will be a useful business application.
And it's going to really wrap up this week of learning about hugging face and open source.
So looking forward to it.
I will see you then.