Well, welcome to the final part on rag.
And this is the session where you go from being a rag expert to being a rag master.
Uh, we are going to look today at a few things.
We're going to look at the Lang chain, LCL, the Lang chain expression language, which is where we
look at the declarative language for setting up these chains.
Uh, and it's not something we're going to use in earnest, but we'll take a look at it.
I'm going to talk a bit about how Lang Chain works behind the scenes, and we're going to fix and diagnose
some common problems that come up with rag.
And there's something else, something else that I just slipped in because I couldn't resist it.
Something that I said we could do that was really easy.
Uh, and I want to show you that we certainly can.
And in fact, we're going to do that right away.
So before we get on with the rest of today's activities, I'm going to take you to JupyterLab and show
you something that I just knocked up to prove a little point, but to also illustrate another vector
database.
See you there.