Well, congratulations on leveling up yet again.
You've got some real hard skills that you've added to your arsenal.
Uh, it's, uh, been a really, really enjoyable last few lectures.
So at this point, not only can you confidently use OpenAI's API, not only can you throw Anthropic
and Gemini into the mix, but you can also build UIs for your solution.
Doing reasonably sophisticated things like pick between models and make changes to prompts, and generate
company brochures with markdown and streaming.
Uh, it's all pretty, uh, high functionality stuff, so well done.
Tomorrow, though, uh, we raised the bar again.
We'll be able to build chat UIs in Gradio, so these are more complex UIs with much more going on with
like, an instant message style interaction.
It sounds complex.
We'll see if it is.
Uh, we're going to talk about providing more context in a prompt, including Multi-shot prompting something
which hopefully you already experimented with a bit in some of the earlier exercises, and we'll keep
going with that.
And ultimately we're going to build a customer support assistant.
We're going to build a real tool and see how that works.
And that's all happening starting in the next lecture.
And I'll see you there.